zamm.com 2018-12-22

# Privacy Policy - Zamm.com | My Movies

This On-Line Privacy Policy includes details about the type of information we may collect as a result of your use of this website and the potential scope of our use of such collected information. You acknowledge and agree that ZAMM.com and/or its affiliated companies may collect, use and disclose the data collected in the course of our relationship in the manner identified in our Privacy Policy. PLEASE NOTE THAT THE PRIVACY POLICY MAY CHANGE FROM TIME TO TIME AND YOU SHOULD CHECK OUR PRIVACY POLICY FREQUENTLY FOR THE MOST CURRENT APPLICABLE TERMS.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

### Information We Collect

_Personally Identifiable Information â€“_ This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. It includes but is not limited to your name, age, mailing address, phone number, e-mail address, employer, and job function. We request Personally Identifiable Information when you register to use any on-line system, order a product or service, participate in certain promotional activities, fill out surveys, and correspond with us. Once you register and sign in, you are not anonymous to us. The personally identifiable data we collect when you visit the Site may include the Uniform Resource Locator (â€œURLâ€) of the Web site that you came from before visiting the Site, which pages you visit on the Site, which URL you next go to, which browser you used to come to the Site, your platform, your user name, your Internet Protocol (â€œIPâ€) address, and any search terms entered on the Site. We use industry-accepted standards and technology (including â€˜cookiesâ€™ *) to collect this data and also take reasonable and up-to-date measures to maintain the security and integrity of collected data.

### Why We Collect this Information

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide our customers and other users with superior service and a smooth, efficient, and personalized experience while using the Site. For example, if you purchase products or request information on the Site, we may use your Personally Identifiable Information to fill your order or provide the requested information. We may use Personally Identifiable Information to analyze customer behavior to help us understand how users use the Site and to measure interest in the various pages. We may use this information to improve the content of the Site and to make the Site easier to use.

### How We Use Your Information

We gather and may use information in a number of ways, including the following:

  * _Browsing and Searching â€“_ We collect certain Personally Identifiable Information when you visit the Site or click on the various links for products and services. We collect this information to help run the Site more efficiently, to gather broad demographic information, to monitor the level of activity on the Site, and possibly to evaluate the effectiveness of any of our advertising.
  * _Ordering â€“_ We collect Personally Identifiable Information when you purchase products and services. We collect this information to deliver your order, to obtain payment, and to communicate with you about the status of your order.
  * _Technical Support â€“_ We may collect certain information when you request technical support for ZAMM.com and/or its affiliate products or companies. This information is necessary to identify your systems, understand the configuration of the products, diagnose your questions, and provide solutions.
  * _Online Surveys and Polling â€“_ We collect Personally Identifiable Information from customers who volunteer to complete surveys or participate in polls. We may use this information to improve our products and services.
  * _Promotional Activities â€“_ We collect Personally Identifiable Information from you when you enter a promotional program or activity. We may use this information to administer the program or activity, to send you promotional e-mails, notify winners, and make the winnersâ€™ list publicly available pursuant to applicable regulations and laws.
  * _Newsletters and Promotional E-mails â€“_ We collect Personally Identifiable Information when you ask to receive newsletters, promotional e-mails, and other information. We use this information to provide you the information you request.
  * _Contact Information â€“_ If you contact us, we keep a record of your correspondence or comments, including Personally Identifiable Information, in a file specific to you. We may use this information to help us provide you better service in the event you contact us again.

### Sharing Your Information

We do not sell, trade, or rent to others the Personally Identifiable Information we collect online. We may share the Personally Identifiable Information you provide online only with other ZAMM.com affiliate entities and/or businesses that provide services to ZAMM.com and its affiliates and only for the purposes described above. Where ZAMM.com and/or its affiliate companies engages third parties to perform services on our behalf, we will require them to observe the intent of this On-line Privacy Policy statement.

From time to time, we may be required to provide Personally Identifiable Information in response to a court order, subpoena, or government investigation. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may release certain Personally Identifiable Information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves. It is also possible that ZAMM.com and/or its related entities could merge with or be acquired by another business entity or their respective assets could be acquired. Should such a merger or acquisition occur, it is likely ZAMM.com and/or affiliate companies would share some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information to continue serving you and other users of the Site.

ZAMM Privacy Policy 1_1

* * *
